ILGWU. Local 155 records 5780/054
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Local 155 records
1930-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 155
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/054
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Articles, reports, minutes, correspondence, newsletters.
The Local 155 records consist primarily of the correspondence of Louis Nelson, manager of Local 15. The activities of the local are documented through articles, speeches, and other materials from the depression years through the late 1960s. Also included are minutes of Local 155's Executive Board between 1979 and 1995, issues of the local's publication, Knitgood Workers' Voice, from 1937 to 1995, files on Joe Lombardo and the Local 155's Health and Welfare Fund.
3798298
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
D. Mordente, October 13, 2008
EAD encoding:
Kathryn Dowgiewicz, June 11, 2014
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States, the ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. In 1995, the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Biographical / Historical
Local 155, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), also known as the Knitgoods Workers' Union, was chartered in 1933 and based in New York City.
Scope and Contents
The Local 155 records consist primarily of the correspondence of Louis Nelson, manager of Local 155 during the period. There are also articles, speeches, and other materials, as well as a small amount of Nelson's personal correspondence.
The correspondence arranged alphabetically by subject and the material documents the activities and concerns of the Local's leadership from the depression years through the late 1960s. In addition to routine Local administrative matters, the materials cover a wide variety of topics, including anti-Semitism, civil rights issues, health and retirement benefits, the women's clothing industry, New York City elections, political activities of the Local, relations with other unions, forced labor in the Soviet Union, the Spanish Civil War, strikes, and union elections.
Individual correspondents represented in the collection include Angela Balabanoff, Fred Beal, B.J. Bialostotzky, David Dubinsky, Melech Epstein, Fiorello LaGuardia, Elias Lieberman, Jay Lovestone, Norman Thomas, and Carlo Tresca. Organizations include the AFL-CIO, the American Labor Party, the Italian-American Labor Council, the Jewish Labor Committee, the Liberal Party of New York, the National Urban League, the Socialist Party, the Union for Democratic Socialism, the United Textile Workers Union of America, and Workmen's Circle.
Subjects that are well documented include elections. The union and local actively supported the Liberal Party. But of interest are the files regarding elections within the local. There were various factions vying for leadership positions in the local, including the Rank and File candidates who were running against the incumbent Progressive Group and manager Louis Nelson.
The collection also offers a look at the knitgood industry, through reports by manager Nelson to the General Executive Board (GEB). Additionally, the industry can be studied through the companies, manufacturer associations such as the United Knitwear Manufacturers League and the Knitted Outerwear Manufacturers Association, as well as industry publications "United Knitwear Reporter" and "Associated Knitwear Contractors News."
Another component of the collection are the minutes of the Executive Board for the Knitgoods Workers' Union Local 155. There are also minutes for various committees of the local including the Finance, Board of Trustees for the Retirement Board, Education, Appeals and Grievance Committees. Additionally, there are volumes from the Local 155 publication "Knitgoods Workers Voice" and various publications regarding wages, hours, hearings and recommendations regarding the knitwear industry. At the end of the collection appear reports and transcripts of the proceedings before the National Labor Relations Board in the case of Amberton Knitting Mills and Local 155.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/129: ILGWU. Local 155 records
Antisemitism -- United States; Civil rights -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Elections--New York (State)--New York.; Forced labor -- Soviet Union; Health insurance -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Officials and employees; Labor unions -- Political activities; Labor union locals; Pension trusts -- New York (State) -- New York; Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State) -- New York; Women's clothing industry -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (N.Y.) -- Politics and government -- 20th century; Spain -- History -- Civil War, 1936-1939; Balabanoff, Angelica, 1878-1965.; Beal, Fred Erwin, 1896-1954.; Bialostotzky, B. J.(Benjamin Jacob), 1892-1962.; Dubinsky, David, 1892-1982.; Epstein, Melech.; La Guardia, Fiorello H.(Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.; Lieberman, Elias, b. 1888-; Nelson, Louis.; Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968.; Tresca, Carlo, 1879-1943.; AFL-CIO; American Labor Party; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 155 (New York, N.Y.); Italian-American Labor Council; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.); Liberal Party of New York State; National Urban League; Socialist Party (U.S.); Union for Democratic Socialism; United Textile Workers of America; Workmen's Circle/Arbeter Ring
3798298
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Controversy.
- American Jewish League Against Communism, Inc., 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Labor Party, 1936-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Labor for Peace and Democracy, and American Peace Mobilization, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- American Youth Congress, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Anti-Semitism, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Proceedings, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Between Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Shirt Manufacturers, Inc., et. al. and Joint Boar of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers Union.
- Arrests For Striking, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Articles, Speeches, Statements, 1930-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Louis Nelson and others on Union and non-Union matters.
- B, 1939-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Balabanoff, Angelica, 1939-1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Beal, Fred E., 1940-1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bialostotzky, B.J., 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Brooklyn Association for Rehabilitation of Offenders, Inc. (B.A.R.D.), 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bund, 1942-1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Incl. American Representation of the General Jewish Workers Union of Poland; Coordinating Committees of the Bund, and Affiliated Jewish Socialist Organizations in various countries
- Business Agents, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- C, 1940-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cleveland Strike, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Incl. letters from Emile DeLeo (organizer) on strikes in knitgoods mills and AFL and CIO involvement.
- Communist Party, 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Communist Party, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Morning Freiheit.
- Congratulatory Messages, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  April 1952. Re Louis Nelson's election as V.P. of the Union.
- Contributions, 1936-1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Incl. relief during war period.
- Contributions, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Conventions, Union, 1934-1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Incl. Local resolutions.
- Credit Union, 1944-1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Knitgoods Workers.
- D, 1940-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Day Strike, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Deborah Tuberculosis Sanatarium and Hospital, 1950-1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- DeLeo, Emile J., 1939-1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Dubinsky, David, 1942-1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- E, 1941-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Education Committee of G.E.B., 1940-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Incl. ILGWU Training Institute.
- Elections, Liberal Party, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Endorsement of John V. Lindsay for Mayor of New York City.
- Elections, Liberal Party, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Elections, Progressive Group 1935. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Elections, Rank and File Group, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Elections, Rank and File Group, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Elections, Nominations of Candidates, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Elections, Rank and File Group, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Elections, Rank and File Group, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Elections, Progressive Group, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Elections' Rank and File Group, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Elections, Progressive and Rank & File Groups., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Elections, Progressive Slate, and Rank & File Group, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Elections, Progressive Slate and Rank & File Group, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Elections, Progressive Slate and Rank & File Group, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Elections, Progressive Slate and Rank & File Group, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Epstein, Melech, 1941-1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Erlich, Henryk, and Victor Alter, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- F, 1940-1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Firms, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- France, 1940-1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Free Jewish Club, New York, 1940-1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Free Trade Union Committee, 1948-1955 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Freeland League, 1946-1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Incl. I.N. Sternberg letters.
- G, 1939-1955 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Gantner and Mattern Strike, San Francisco, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Incl. local report.
- Germany, 1935-1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Goldberg, Harry and Rose, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- H, 1940-1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Health, Welfare and Retirement, 1939-1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Heller, Philip A. (and Evelyn), 1942-1951 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  1942-July 1951. Letters & reports from Heller, (Labor Informatio Officer) Economic Cooperation Administration (EC in Austria & Germany.
- Heller, Philip A. (and Evelyn), 1951-1954 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  October 1951-1954.
- Hornlek, Louis, and Co., N.Y.C., 1940-1947 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- I, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Il Martello, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Il Progresso Italo-American, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  April 8, 1943.
- International Indemnity Committee, 1946-1950 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Incl. letters from Philip Heller; reports on Spanish situation.
- Israel, 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Italian-American Labor Council, 1943-1952 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Italy, 1940-1950 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- J, 1940-1954 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1944-1946 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1947-1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Incl. correspondence w. Jacob Pat & David Dubinsky re Nelson's resignation from JLC (Nov. 1947), and articles.
- Jewish Newsletter, 1949-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Jurisdictional Disputes, 1939-1943 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- K, 1936-1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Kampelman, Max, 1942-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Knitgoods Industry [folder 1 of 2], 1937-1955 (Box 7, Folder 5a)
  Miscellaneous.
- Knitgoods Industry [folder 2 of 2], 1937-1955 (Box 7, Folder 5b)
- Knitgoods Unions. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Incl. Knitgoods Workers Industrial Union of the Needle Trades Workers Industrial Union.
- Knitted Outerwear Times, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Published by National Knitted Outerwear Association.
- Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc., United, 1937-1955 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Correspondence.
- Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc. United [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 9a)
  1940-Feb. 1943. Publication, United Knitwear Reporter.
- Knitwear Manufacturers League, Inc. United [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 9b)
- Knitwear News, Associated, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Published by the Associated Knitwear Contractors Inc.
- L, 1941-1955 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Labor Department, U.S., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- LaGuardia, Fiorello, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1941-1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Legislation, Labor, 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Liberal Party, 1944-1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Lieberman, Elias, 1940-1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Locals, (Misc.), 1942-1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Local 22, 1939-1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Local 89, 1947-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Lovestone, Jay, 1938-1949 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- M, 1940-1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- May Day, 1937-1952 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- N, 1940-1956 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- National Urban League, 1941-1947 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Incl. corres. w. A. Philip Randolph & Frank B. Crosswaith; draft article by L. Nelson.
- Needle Trades Progressive Group, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Council Meetings.
- Negotiations, 1938-1956 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Nelson Family, 1940-1950 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- New York Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt-and Reefer Makers' Union, 1939-1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- New York Dress Joint Board, 1944-1952 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Nold, John E., 1945-1954 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Corres. re his case (clemency for murder).
- O, 1941-1949 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Office and Professional Workers of America, United, 1930-1939 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Corres. w. Nicholas Kirtzman.
- P, 1939-1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Personnel, 1933-1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- R, 1940-1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Racism, 1943-1947 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Refugees, Anti-Fascist, 1939-1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Resolution from workers in knitting mills in support of Local 155 and against the United Textile Workers Union, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Russia, 1941-1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Incl. material on labor camps.
- S, 1940-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Socialist Party, U.S.A., 1943-1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Soderberg, Jack, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Spanish Civil War, 1938-1953 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Strikes, 1936-1940 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Knitgoods industry.
- T, 1942-1956 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Taksen, Jack, 1940-1956 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Textile Workers Union of America, United, 1933-1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Thomas, Norman, 1941-1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Incl. corres. re Carlo Tresca murder & Memorial.
- Tresca, Carlo (and Margaret De Silver), 1940-1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Incl. corres. re Carlo Tresca Memorial Fund.
- U, 1944-1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Union for Democratic Socialism, 1953-1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Incl. James T. Farrell letter to Norman Thomas outlining a general political program (n.d.).
- Unions, 1940-1949 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Printed material.
- Unity House, 1941-1954 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- V, 1943-1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- W, 1940-1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Wallerstein, Jacob, 1939-1956 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  And his poems.
- Workmen's Circle, 1942-1954 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Knitgood Workers branch.
- World War II, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Incl. statements from Keep America Out of War Congress & Other anti-war groups.
- World War II, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Displaced Persons.
- World War II, 1940-1945 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Government & labor.
- World War II, 1941-1943 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Russian War Relief.
- X, Y, Z, 1940-1953 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Yiddish Scientific Institute (YIVO), 1940-1954 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Zionism, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Minutes. Executive Board. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  October 12, 1933 - June 1934
- Minutes. Executive Board. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 1793, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  September 1933 - June 1934
- Minutes. Executive Board. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1934-1937 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  October 1934 - December 1937
- Minutes. Executive Board. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1934-1937 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  October 1934 - September 1937
- Minutes. Joint Council. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1934-1937 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  September 1934 - October 1937
- Minutes. Executive Board. Local 155, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  January 1938 - December 1939
- Minutes. Executive Board. Local 155, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  January 1940 - December 1941
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  January 1941 - December 1942
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  January 1943 - December 1943
- Minutes. Executive Board. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  January 1944 - December 1944
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Local 155, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Local 155, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  January 1945 - December 1945
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  January 1946 - December 1946
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  January 1947 - December 1947
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  January 1948 - December 1948
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  January 1949 - December 1949
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  January 1950 - December 1950
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  January 1951 - December 1951
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  January 1952 - December 1952
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgood Workers Union. Local 155, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  January 1953 - December 1953
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  January 1954 - December 1954
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  January 1955 - December 1955
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  January 1956 - December 1956
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  January 1957 - December 1958
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  January 1959 - December 1959
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meeting. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  January 1960 - December 1960
- Minutes. Finance Committee. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1934-1942 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  October 1934 - December 1942
- Minutes. Knitgoods Workers Retirement Fund Board of Trustees Meetings. Volume I. (1 of 2), 1949-1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  June 7, 1949 - September 13, 1957
- Minutes. Knitgoods Workers Retirement Fund Board of Trustees Meetings. Volume I. (2 of 2), 1949-1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Minutes. Knitgoods Workers Retirement Fund Board of Trustees Meetings. Volume II. (1 of 2), 1958-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  February 27, 1958 - May 27, 1969
- Minutes. Knitgoods Workers Retirement Fund Board of Trustees Meetings. Volume II. (2 of 2), 1958-1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Minutes. Finance Committee. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  June 1946 - December 1952
- Minutes. Appeals Committee and Grievance Board. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1946-1952 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Appeals Committee, August 1946 - December 1947. Grievance Board, January 1958 - December 1952
- Minutes. Educational Committee. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  January 1949 - December 1952
- Minutes. Membership Committee. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Minutes. Finance, Educational and Membership Committees & Grievance Board. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1953- 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  January 1953 - December 1954
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  January 1961 - December 1961
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  January 1962 - December 1962
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  January 1963 - December 1963
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  January 1964 - December 1964
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  January 1965 - December 1965
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  January 1966 - December 1966
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  January 1967 - December 1967
- Minutes. Executive Board Membership Meetings. Knitgoods Workers Union. Local 155, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  January 1968 - December 1968
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. I, No.1-Vol.V, No.6, 1937-1941 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. VI, No.1-Vol. VIII, No. 6, 1942-1944 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. IX, No.1-Vol.Vol. XIII, No.5, 1945-1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. XV, No.1-Vol. XV, No.5, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Knitgood Workers Voice. Vol. XV, No.1- Vol. XVI, No.7, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. XX, No.1-Vol.XXI, No.5, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. XXII, No.1-Vol. XXVII, No.7, 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Knitgoods Workers Voice. Vol. XXVIII, No.1-Vol. XXIX, No.5, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- "Forty Cent Minimum Wage for the Women's Apparel Industry." Memorandum by Lazare Teper., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- "Knitted Outerwear Industry" Report. U.S. Dept. of Labor, Wage and Hour Division. Research & Statistics Branch., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Public Hearing Before Special Interest Committee for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Public Hearing Before Special Interest Committee for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Area Differences in the Cost of Living. Wage and Hour Division., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Report on Knitted Outerwear Industry. Economic Section, Wage and Hour Division., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Executive Sessions Hearing: Indsutry Committee No. 7 for the Knitted Outerwear Industry., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 15)